Crayon Shinchan
Subbed by X-Anime | Telegram
stay a little away from your device! - by shinnosuke
Well I guess it's time for us to go
It's noisy
Be quiet before being taken to use
I want to be used by a pretty lady
It's impossible, because this is a kindergarten
But that's not what we crayons are about
The most important is to be able to used up till the end
That's a happy crayon life
right!
Well, now that we're all here, shall we do what we always do?
Red crayon!
Blue crayon!
Green crayon!
Yellow crayon!
Pink crayon!
all 5 together
5 color of crayons
well, that's just as it should be
You made me do it.
So comfortable
Paint more!
I like it. Red and Pink are popular with girls.
You have a problem with that
Because the times are Gender free
Boys can also like red and pink
There's nothing wrong with that
The color you like is your own choice
Yeah, but...
That's doctor yellow
The boy who likes trams
Bo, you've decreased a lot
Completed the mission perfectly
Kazama-kun is a self proclaimed elite crayon, but..
It's not used very often
Because I and Masao are natural colors
I play an important role in landscape painting
But the kids in this group..
It seems he's not painting a natural landscape
Okay, let's go to the other group
lla lla
Wait a minute
ah!
Let's go, be careful not to get stepped on
Ola, I want to paint my swimsuit
Watch out!
This way! Quickly!
Oh, no, it fell out
Bo-chan Thank you
Kazama-kun
That must be a picture of the ocean
Alright, when it comes to the sea, it's blue
it's coming, it's coming!
Excellent!
That's Mr. Cobalt blue Koval.
If you have cobalt blue
The kids crayon is are the 36 color type
So many colors, iit's hard to pick just one.
That's shinchan and others
It's great to be taken again
Well, let's go to that group
Alright
wait
Good come on
Oh, it's me again
Oh, my god, she has a good taste to put pink on a bunny
I like it
Everyone look at Nene!
I can't believe I got the rabbit paint at end
I feel great
I used up all my pink
Nene is really lucky
Let's get ours used up as fast as we can
I don't see any kids drawing the sky or the ocean
The girl in swimsuit..
If this happens..
Use me, Use me, Use me
hooray, I did it
This is good one
Fruits..
I have no regrets in my whole life
Even Bo...
What if we just stay like this forever?
No, don't say that
But..
Okay okay
Why are you so calm?
Let's move on to the next
Don't leave me!
Shinnosuke..
I'm in three
Buriburi.. buriburi..
Stop it
I was so worried...
Found green
It's a picture of a forest, finally
Kazama-kun, Shinchan, Good bye
Even Masao has been used up
So why aren't there any picture that use me?
You look a little pale, Mr. Kazama
I am originally this color
What do I do?
I can hear them. they are calling out for me over there
To make sure everyone obeys the signals properly
I have to paint it nice
Stop for red
Oh? this crayon is broken
Not that much
then let's use it all up here.
Kazama-kun, Good night
I'll see you next time
See you..
I don't want to be the only one left... Guys!
sorry to bother you
What's wrong?
I ran out of my crayons
mam told me to get it from the principal
Okay, well, you can take any color you like
This color
is blue enough?
Hoi! Thank you, leader
I am the principal
Yo! Coloring.. coloring
Thank you
Finished!